Guide to the Communications Workers of America Records WAG.124
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: Departments/Divisions/Districts, 1937-1991
  - Subseries VIII:C: CWA Departments, 1937-1991
    - Subsubseries VIII:C:6: Long Lines, Districts, and Locals, 1937-1991
      - Local 3602: Correspondence, 1984 (Box 239, Folder 78)
      - Local 3603: Correspondence, 1984 (Box 239, Folder 79)
      - Local 3611: Correspondence, 1984 (Box 239, Folder 80)
      - Local 3616: Correspondence, undated (Box 239, Folder 81)
      - Local 3650: Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 239, Folder 82)
      - Local 3706: Correspondence, 1984 (Box 239, Folder 83)
      - Local 10950: Correspondence, 1977-1984 (Box 239, Folder 84)
      - Installation: Correspondence, 1975, 1980 (Box 240, Folder 1)
      - Installation: Correspondence, Jan 1982-Mar 1982 (Box 240, Folder 2)
      - Installation: Correspondence, Apr 1982-Aug 1982 (Box 240, Folder 3)
      - Installation: Letters and Corr., Sep 1982-Dec 1982 (Box 240, Folder 4)
      - Installation: Bulletins & Corr., Jan 1983-Feb 1983 (Box 240, Folder 5)
      - Installation: Bulletins; Correspondence, Mar 1983-Jul 1983 (Box 240, Folder 6)
      - Installation: Bulletins; Correspondence, Aug 1983-Oct 1983 (Box 240, Folder 7)
      - Installation: Bulletins Sent Out; Correspondence, Nov 1983-Dec 1983 (Box 240, Folder 8)
      - Installation: Bulletins Sent Out; Correspondence, Jan 1984-Feb 1984 (Box 240, Folder 9)
      - Installation: Letters and Correspondence, Mar 1984-Apr 1984 (Box 240, Folder 10)
      - Installation: Letters and Correspondence, May 1984-Jun 1984 (Box 240, Folder 11)
      - Installation: Letters and Correspondence, Jul 1984-Aug 1984 (Box 240, Folder 12)
      - Installation: Letters and Correspondence, Sep 1984-Dec 1984 (Box 240, Folder 13)
      - Installation: Letters and Correspondence, Sep 1985-Oct 1985 (Box 240, Folder 14)
      - Installation: Letters and Correspondence, Nov 1985-Dec 1985 (Box 240, Folder 15)
      - O-J-T, AT&T, Long Lines Department, 1947 (Box 240, Folder 16)
      - AT&T, Long Lines Department: Pension Materials, 1949, 1953, 1981 (Box 240, Folder 17)
      - Insurance; Medical: Bell System Bargaining, 1981, undated (Box 240, Folder 18)
      - AT&T- Medical Expense Plan; Manual of Standard Adm. Practice, 1981-1985 (Box 240, Folder 19)
      - Long Lines: CWA-Working File - Correspondence; Grievances, 1982-1986 (Box 241, Folder 1)
      - Long Lines: CWA/AT&T-T-C Meetings, 1983-1986 (Box 241, Folder 2)
      - Long Lines: Cost-Containment, 1983-1985 (Box 241, Folder 3)
      - Long Lines: New Craft Test, 1983-1986 (Box 241, Folder 4)
      - Long Lines: AT&T- Financial Reports/Correspondence/State Univ of NJ-Rutgers, 1983-1985 (Box 241, Folder 5)
      - Long Lines: Four-Day Work Week, 1984 (Box 241, Folder 6)
      - Long Lines: Green Circle Problems, 1984 (Box 241, Folder 7)
      - Long Lines: Upgrade/Transfer, 1984-1985 (Box 241, Folder 8)
      - Long Lines: CWA- Internal Political Activity, 1984-1986 (Box 241, Folder 9)
      - Long Lines: Office Closings, 1984-1986 (Box 241, Folder 10)
      - Long Lines: AT&T Communications- "Introduction to Basic Finance", 1985 (Box 241, Folder 11)
      - Long Lines: Employee Assistance Program - AT&T/CWA, 1985 (Box 241, Folder 12)
      - Long Lines: Organizing/Developing New Tactics: AT&T Sup. Pac, 1985 (Box 241, Folder 13)
      - Long Lines: CWA / AT&T Negotiations, 1985 (Box 241, Folder 14)
      - Long Lines: Press; Public Relations: Correspondence; Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 241, Folder 15)
      - Long Lines: AT&T: Training; Re-training, 1985-1986 (Box 241, Folder 16)
      - Long Lines: New Craft Test Book, 1986 (Box 241, Folder 17)
      - Long Lines: Data/ Regional Processing Center Project / Bargaining Q&A, 1986 (Box 241, Folder 18)
      - Long Lines: CWA Convention, 1986 (Box 241, Folder 19)
      - Long Lines: Arb. Award AT&T & A.B.T.W, 1947 (Box 241, Folder 20)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration: Long Lines (Opinion & Award), 1969 (Box 241, Folder 21)
      - Long Lines: Sex Discrimination Cases, 1969-1971 (Box 241, Folder 22)
      - Long Lines: CWA/AT&T, Aug 20, 1970 (Box 241, Folder 23)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration, Dec 1971 (Box 241, Folder 24)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration: W. E. and CWA F.C. McCarthy Suspension, Apr 11, 1972 (Box 241, Folder 25)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration: W. E. & CWA: Paul W. Siebert, Jul 26, 1972 (Box 241, Folder 26)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration: Blue Cross - Blue Shield, Aug 31, 1972 (Box 241, Folder 27)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration: W. E. & Bell Labs, Sep 5, 1972 (Box 241, Folder 28)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration Awards (1 of 7), 1984-1985 (Box 241, Folder 29)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration Awards (2 of 7), 1984-1985 (Box 241, Folder 30)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration Awards (3 of 7), 1984-1985 (Box 241, Folder 31)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration Awards (4 of 7), 1984-1985 (Box 241, Folder 32)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration Awards (5 of 7), 1984-1985 (Box 241, Folder 33)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration Awards (6 of 7), 1984-1985 (Box 241, Folder 34)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration Awards (7 of 7), 1984-1985 (Box 241, Folder 35)
      - Long Lines: EEOC Affirmative Action Program 1st, 1973, 1982, 1989 (Box 242, Folder 1)
      - Long Lines: EEOC Affirmative Action Program 2nd, 1972-1977 (Box 242, Folder 2)
      - Long Lines: EEOC Affirmative Action Program 3rd, 1970-1975 (Box 242, Folder 3)
      - Long Lines: Legal: Labor law Developments: 1st, 1981-1982, 1989 (Box 242, Folder 4)
      - Long Lines: Legal: Labor law Developments: 2nd, 1964-1980 (Box 242, Folder 5)
      - Long Lines: Legal Opinions, 1963-1985 (Box 242, Folder 6)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration: Awards, Rulings, etc, 1971-1989 (Box 242, Folder 7)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration: Cumulative Digest & Analysis of CWA Arbitration Awards, 1978 (Box 242, Folder 8)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration List, 1984, 1985 (Box 242, Folder 9)
      - Long Lines: Expedited Arbitration, 1976-1981 (Box 242, Folder 10)
      - Long Lines: Arbitrators List, District 1, 1981 (Box 242, Folder 11)
      - Long Lines: M.P.S. 22, 1977-1978 (Box 242, Folder 12)
      - Long Lines: IBEW/ORTT 1st. Folder, 1977-1984 (Box 242, Folder 13)
      - Long Lines: IBEW/ORTT 2nd Folder, 1980-1983 (Box 242, Folder 14)
      - Long Lines: Nattie Queen Arbitration Brief, 1978, 1988 (Box 242, Folder 15)
      - Long Lines:AT&T Long Lines Department Case #2-CA-15298, 1978 (Box 242, Folder 16)
      - Long Lines: Selection of Arbitrators, Apr 16, 1979, Sep 24, 1990, 1990 (Box 242, Folder 17)
      - Long Lines: Strikes Unemployment, 1980 (Box 242, Folder 18)
      - Long Lines: Service Representatives, 1980, 1981 (Box 242, Folder 19)
      - Long Lines: CWA's Address Changes for Locals, 1981-1984 (Box 242, Folder 20)
      - Long Lines: Legislative: Senate Bill S. 1660, 1981-1984 (Box 242, Folder 21)
      - Long Lines: AFL-CIO Article 20, 1982 (Box 242, Folder 22)
      - Long Lines: Trial Court Decision- CWA Local 6016, 1983 (Box 242, Folder 23)
      - Long Lines: Request for Legal Opinion 1983 and 1984, 1983-1984 (Box 242, Folder 24)
      - Long Lines: International Affairs, 1984 (Box 242, Folder 25)
      - Long Lines: Southwestern Bell Telephone Arbitration Case #71-30-0041-84, 1985 (Box 242, Folder 26)
      - Long Lines: Employee Protection Legislation Update, 1985 (Box 242, Folder 27)
      - Long Lines: 1986 Bargaining, 1985 (Box 242, Folder 28)
      - Long Lines: CWA Legal Department Corr, 1985, 1989 (Box 242, Folder 29)
      - Long Lines: Jim Irvine's Testimony- Subcommittee on Communications: U.S. Senate, 1985, 1989 (Box 242, Folder 30)
      - Long Lines: FCC Docket No. 85-26, 1986 (Box 242, Folder 31)
      - Long Lines: Grievance Local 9415, 1986, 1987 (Box 242, Folder 32)
      - Long Lines: Request for Legal Opinion '86 and '87, 1987 (Box 242, Folder 33)
      - Long Lines: Morella P. Riley vs. CWA Locals 9415 & 4050, 1987 (Box 242, Folder 34)
      - Long Lines: CC Docket No., 87-611, 1987-1988 (Box 242, Folder 35)
      - Long Lines: EEOC & CWA vs. AT&T; Chicago; Pregnancy Class Action, 1988 (Box 242, Folder 36)
      - Long Lines: Arbitrator Donald P. Goodman Ft. worth Texas, 1988 (Box 242, Folder 37)
      - Long Lines: Bache vs. ATTIS & CWA U.S. Court of Appeals 5th circuit, 1988 (Box 242, Folder 38)
      - Long Lines: Patrick Scanlon's Corr, 1988-1989 (Box 242, Folder 39)
      - Long Lines: Appeal of Ted Esch. Case NO. 22-CB-6015, 1989 (Box 242, Folder 40)
      - Long Lines: Price Caps CC Docket #87-313, 1989 (Box 242, Folder 41)
      - Long Lines: 1989 Labor Negotiation, 1990 (Box 242, Folder 42)
      - Long Lines: CWA Legislative Fact Sheet, 1998 (Box 242, Folder 43)
      - Long Lines: EEOC Bell Companies, 1973 (Box 243, Folder 1)
      - Long Lines: EEOC, CWA vs. AT&T: U.S. District Court: Chicago Pregnancy/Maternity, 1987 (Box 243, Folder 2)
      - Long Lines: CA-80-0208 Eastern District of Penn, 1980 (Box 243, Folder 3)
      - Long Lines: CA-82-0192 CWA's Comments to Department of Justice Order, 1987 (Box 243, Folder 4)
      - Long Lines: CA-87-0455-OG Court Decision - CWA vs. Bell Atlantic, 1987 (Box 243, Folder 5)
      - Long Lines: CA No. 82-0192 U.S.A. v. Western Electric Company, Inc, 1988 (Box 243, Folder 6)
      - Long Lines: CA-82-0192 Judge Greene - Relaxation of the Consent Decree, undated (Box 243, Folder 7)
      - Long Lines: CA No. 88-2754-H Miguel Moreno vs. AT&T Tech., Inc, 1989 (Box 243, Folder 8)
      - Long Lines: CA-89-8150 CWA vs. AT&T, 1991 (Box 243, Folder 9)
      - Long Lines: IBEW/ORTT, 1982-1984 (Box 243, Folder 10)
      - Long Lines: State Anti-Monitoring Legislation, 1983 (Box 243, Folder 11)
      - Long Lines: 82-0025 & 82-0192 Western Electric & AT&T, 1983 (Box 243, Folder 12)
      - Long Lines: Local Union Liability - Illegal Work Stoppage, 1983 (Box 243, Folder 13)
      - Long Lines: Hauk, et. al. vs. Western Electric Company and CWA, 1983 (Box 243, Folder 14)
      - Long Lines: Concerned Women Advancement. Committee (CWAC), 1983 (Box 243, Folder 15)
      - Long Lines: Article 20- IBEW Case 83-26-Long Lines; IBEW - IL Bell, 1983 (Box 243, Folder 16)
      - Long Lines: Article 20- CWA vs. IBEW: Illinois Long Lines (Case 83-26), 1983 (Box 243, Folder 17)
      - Long Lines: Court Case CWA/IBEW (Chicago 8) Local 5050 (83-26), 1983 (Box 243, Folder 18)
      - Long Lines: HR 4102/S. 1660 Legislation, 1983 (Box 243, Folder 19)
      - Long Lines: HR 1950 Monitoring Legislation, 1985-1987 (Box 243, Folder 20)
      - Long Lines: HR 4154 The Bill of Mandatory Retirement, 1986 (Box 243, Folder 21)
      - Long Lines: HR 1562 Informational Trade, 1986 (Box 243, Folder 22)
      - Long Lines: HR 162 High Risk Occupational Discase Notification and Prevention Act, 1987 (Box 243, Folder 23)
      - Long Lines: HR 1950 Secret Telephone Monitoring, 1987 (Box 243, Folder 24)
      - Long Lines: HR 1049 Dorgan Tax Bill and Neutrality in Organizing, 1988 (Box 243, Folder 25)
      - Long Lines: HR 2168 Monitoring Bill, May 24, 1989 (Box 243, Folder 26)
      - Long Lines: HR 2140 Telecommunication Anti-Worker Bill, undated (Box 243, Folder 27)
      - Long Lines: AT&T Communications Case #10-CA-20171, 1985 (Box 243, Folder 28)
      - Long Lines: AT&T Communications Case #25-CA-17177, 1985 (Box 243, Folder 29)
      - Long Lines: AT&T Information Systems, Inc. Case #26-CA-12084, 1987 (Box 243, Folder 30)
      - Long Lines: AT&T Technologies Maternity Leave Litigation Western Electric, 1989 (Box 243, Folder 31)
      - Long Lines: AT&T. NLRB (Case 22- CA 0 16132), 1989 (Box 243, Folder 32)
      - Long Lines: Leslie vs. CWA, 1989 (Box 243, Folder 33)
      - Long Lines: S-2565 Dole Bill, 1986 (Box 243, Folder 34)
      - Long Lines: S-2282 Legislation to Ban Cheap Handguus, 1988 (Box 243, Folder 35)
      - Long Lines: S. 2621 Increase Minimum Wage, 1989 (Box 243, Folder 36)
      - Long Lines: S. 55 Replacement of Strikers, 1991 (Box 243, Folder 37)
      - Long Lines: Case #14-CA-17028 Increase in Work Hours, 1983-1985 (Box 243, Folder 38)
      - Long Lines: Case # 4-CA-14229 and Case # 4-CB-4795, 1984 (Box 243, Folder 39)
      - Long Lines: Case #88-2754-H Miguel Moreno vs. AT&T, Technologies Inc, 1989 (Box 243, Folder 40)
      - Long Lines: Case No. 90C 6597: Judge Aspen- Steve G. Tisza, vs. CWA, 1990 (Box 243, Folder 41)
      - Long Lines: 87-2242-5 Anthony Derincentis, 1988 (Box 243, Folder 42)
      - Long Lines: 87-3007, 87-3327 R.A. Bache, 1988 (Box 243, Folder 43)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #2-CB-5014 AT&T Withdrawal of Change, 1969, 1971 (Box 243, Folder 44)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #16-CA-4645 AT&T Dismissed Bob Harris, 1972 (Box 243, Folder 45)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #5-CB-2299 AT&T and Harry Nelson, 1977 (Box 243, Folder 46)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #9-CA-11062 AT&T Appeal Denied, 1977 (Box 243, Folder 47)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #9-CA-11279 AT&T Appeal Denied, 1977 (Box 243, Folder 48)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #9-CA-12833 AT&T Imposed Discipline, 1978 (Box 243, Folder 49)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #9-CA-12833 AT&T, 1978 (Box 243, Folder 50)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #9-CA-13031 AT&T Bob Mver, 1978 (Box 243, Folder 51)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #10-CA-13474 AT&T Lines Ordering Rescheduling Hearing, 1978 (Box 243, Folder 52)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #10-CA-13474 AT&T Refusal to Bargain, 1978 (Box 243, Folder 53)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #10-CA-13474 AT&T Phone Concession Reduced, 1978 (Box 243, Folder 54)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #13-CA-16891, 1978 (Box 243, Folder 55)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #13-CA-17479 AT&T Grievance Meeting, 1978 (Box 243, Folder 56)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #041770312 Pauline Moore, 1979 (Box 243, Folder 57)
      - Long Lines: NLRB AT&T Susan Trouten, 1980 (Box 243, Folder 58)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #19-RC-10107 AT&T, 1981 (Box 243, Folder 59)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #81-11 Pacific Telephone &Telegraph Pacific NW Bell, 1981 (Box 243, Folder 60)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Grievance Dan McAleer Company Vehicle, 1981 (Box 243, Folder 61)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #2-CB-9172 AT&T Appeal is Denied, 1982 (Box 243, Folder 62)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #2-CB-9172 Barbara Dawson Notice of Appeal, 1982 (Box 243, Folder 63)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #5 -CA-11932 C & P Telephone, 1981 (Box 243, Folder 64)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #5 -CA-14010 Unfair Labor Practice Change AT&T, 1982 (Box 243, Folder 65)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #8-CA-15386 AT&T Long Lines Unfair Labor Practice, 1982 (Box 243, Folder 66)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #9 -CA-16720 Appraisal Grievance, 1982 (Box 243, Folder 67)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #39-CA-902 AT&T Unfair Labor Practice, 1982 (Box 243, Folder 68)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #29-CA-5241, 1983 (Box 243, Folder 69)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #4-CA-14229 Withdrawn, 1984 (Box 243, Folder 70)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #6 -CB-6631 Unfair Labor Practice Change of Cheryle Randall, 1988 (Box 243, Folder 71)
      - Long Lines: NLRB CWA (AT&T Communication) Case #9-CB-5876, 1984 (Box 243, Folder 72)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #21-CA-23025 AT&T, 1984 (Box 243, Folder 73)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #22-UC-117 TCU Local 213 (1st Folder), 1984 (Box 243, Folder 74)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #22-UC-117 TCU Local 213 (2nd Folder), 1984 (Box 243, Folder 75)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #39-CB-618 and Case #39-CB-625 A. Masse, 1984-1985 (Box 243, Folder 76)
      - Long Lines: NLRB CWA - Case #2-CB-11210, 1985 (Box 243, Folder 77)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #26-CB-2169 Telephone Concession Issue, 1985 (Box 243, Folder 78)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #2 -CC-1911 Strike Related, 1986 (Box 243, Folder 79)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Delbert Johnson - Case #14-CA-19128, 1987 (Box 243, Folder 80)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #30-CA-9802 AT&T Communications, 1987 (Box 243, Folder 81)
      - Long Lines: NLRB CWA Case #30-CB-2788 Grievance. #85-MS-37-7250, 1987 (Box 243, Folder 82)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #22-CA-15137-2 Systems Technician-ULP Charge, 1988 (Box 243, Folder 83)
      - Long Lines: NLRB CWA Case #22-CB-6015, 1989 (Box 243, Folder 84)
      - Long Lines: NLRB Case #13-CB-12670, 1989 (Box 243, Folder 85)
      - Long Lines: Docket No. 74-2191 Long Lines Dept, 1975 (Box 243, Folder 86)
      - Long Lines: A-C-78-127 Failure of Union to Represent, 1981 (Box 243, Folder 87)
      - Long Lines: Supreme Court Decisions: Garcia Decision, 1985 (Box 243, Folder 88)
      - Long Lines: ORTT Work Delineation, 1985 (Box 243, Folder 89)
      - Long Lines: ATTIS NLRB Case #26-CA-12084, 1985, 1987 (Box 243, Folder 90)
      - Long Lines: Legal Expenditures - ATTCOM, 1986 (Box 243, Folder 91)
      - Long Lines: Charge Against AT&T resource Management Case No. 22-RC-9596, 1986 (Box 243, Folder 92)
      - Long Lines: Cline vs. McLeod Georgia SCAB Defomation Case, Nov 16, 1986 (Box 243, Folder 93)
      - Long Lines: 11-85-148 Discharge James Harlan, 1986 (Box 243, Folder 94)
      - Long Lines: Computer III Report, 1986, 1988 (Box 243, Folder 95)
      - Long Lines: Fucetola vs. AT&T and CWA, 1987 (Box 243, Folder 96)
      - Long Lines: Judge Newblatt's Order Granting Legal Fees to CWA, 1988 (Box 243, Folder 97)
      - Long Lines: Trade Bill, 1988 (Box 243, Folder 98)
      - Long Lines: Omnibus Trade Bill, 1988 (Box 243, Folder 99)
      - Long Lines: Skeeter vs. AT&T and CWA: U.S. District Court, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 100)
      - Long Lines: Beck Case: Supreme Court Ruling, 1988 (Box 243, Folder 101)
      - Long Lines: Advance Notification Provision. S. 2527, 1988 (Box 243, Folder 102)
      - Long Lines: Local Telephone Service Deregulation Policy, 1989 (Box 243, Folder 103)
      - Long Lines: Barbara Slaughter: No. 89-2058, 1989 (Box 243, Folder 104)
      - Long Lines: 90-C-6597 Filed by Local 4250, 1990 (Box 243, Folder 105)
      - Long Lines: CWA vs. AT&T Williams/Bahr Letter Litigation, 1990 (Box 243, Folder 106)
      - Long Lines: IBEW Summary Report, 1990 (Box 243, Folder 107)
      - Long Lines: 90C 6597 S. Tisza, vs CWA, undated (Box 243, Folder 108)
      - Long Lines: Docket # ET08NB-28297 Esch. Vs. CWA, 1991 (Box 243, Folder 109)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration Awards- Vol. I (#1)/ Acc #88-1, 1980 (Box 243A, Folder 1)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration Awards- Vol. I (#2)/ Acc #88-1, 1980 (Box 243A, Folder 2)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration Awards- Vol. I (#3)/ Acc #88-1, 1980 (Box 243A, Folder 3)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration Awards- Vol. I (#4)/ Acc #88-1, 1980 (Box 243A, Folder 4)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration Awards- Vol. II (#1)/ Acc #88-1, 1980 (Box 243A, Folder 5)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration Awards- Vol. II (#2)/ Acc #88-1, 1980 (Box 243A, Folder 6)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration Awards- Vol. II (#3)/ Acc #88-1, 1980 (Box 243A, Folder 7)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration Awards- Vol. II (#4)/ Acc #88-1, 1980 (Box 243A, Folder 8)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration Awards- Summaries of Cases, May 13, 1966 (Box 243A, Folder 9)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration Awards- Summaries of Cases, Feb 1, 1969-Oct 31, 1969, 1969 (Box 243A, Folder 10)
      - Long Lines: Arbitration Awards- Summaries of Cases(9/1/67 -2/1/69), Mar 25, 1969 (Box 243A, Folder 11)
      - Long Lines: National Labor Relations BD - CWA Matters, 1943-1954 (Box 243A, Folder 12)
      - Long Lines: Study of an NLRB election -Western Electric, San Ramon, CA, 1972 (Box 243A, Folder 13)
      - Long Lines: National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) -Photocopy Case -CWA, 1977-1979 (Box 243A, Folder 14)
      - Long Lines: National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) -Photocopy Case -CWA, 1979 (Box 243A, Folder 15)
      - Long Lines: National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) -Photocopy Case -CWA, 1981 (Box 243A, Folder 16)
      - Long Lines: National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) -Photocopy Case -CWA, 1981 (Box 243A, Folder 17)
      - Long Lines: National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) -Photocopy Case -CWA, 1981-1982 (Box 243A, Folder 18)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Local 2336-2108 -Complaint, 1983-1984 (Box 243B, Folder 1)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: West Virginia Problems, 1983-1985 (Box 243B, Folder 2)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: WV Local Presidents' Meeting Decision: Gary McCallister Complaints, May 17, 1984 (Box 243B, Folder 3)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Correspondence, Local 2001 President Moss to George Strick, V.P. Dist. 2: McCallister, May 14, 1984 (Box 243B, Folder 4)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Notes, Background, Meetings, Letters on Gary McCallister, Dist.2, WV, 1982-1983 (Box 243B, Folder 5)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Steve Moss, President Local 2001: Gary McCallister, 1980-1983 (Box 243B, Folder 6)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Sue Merrill, Pres. Local 2004: Gary McCallister, 1983 (Box 243B, Folder 7)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Bill Sonnick, Local 2005: Gary McCallister, 1983 (Box 243B, Folder 8)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Willard Johnson, Pres. Local 2007, May 14, 1984 (Box 243B, Folder 9)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Lowell Dameron, Local 2007, ca.1983 (Box 243B, Folder 10)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Jurisdictional Dispute-Local 2100, 1983-1984 (Box 243B, Folder 11)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Local 2108 Worksheets, 1984-1985 (Box 243B, Folder 12)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Disputes - Local 2108 & 2336, 1985 (Box 243B, Folder 13)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Transfer Disputes - Local 2003 - Parkersburg, WV, 1983-1984 (Box 243B, Folder 14)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Local 2336-2108: Complaints, 1984 (Box 243B, Folder 15)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Local 2336-2108: Complaints, 1984 (Box 243B, Folder 16)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Dist.2, WV: Complaints, 1984, 1985 (Box 243B, Folder 17)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Local 2100 and 2101: Jurisdictional Dispute, 1966, 1967, 1979 (Box 243B, Folder 18)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Local 2100 and 2101: Jurisdictional Dispute, 1982 (Box 243B, Folder 19)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Local 2100 and 2101: Jurisdictional Dispute, 1983-1984 (Box 243B, Folder 20)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Local 2336: Pete Catucci Complaints, 1984-1985 (Box 243B, Folder 21)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Dist. 2. WV Local 2003 (Smith): Gary McCallister, 1983 (Box 243B, Folder 22)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Dist. 2. WV: Gary McCallister, 1983 (Box 243B, Folder 23)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: Pledges, Contributions, 1981 (Box 243B, Folder 24)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: City of Hope Program: Contributions, Final Report, CWA Dist.1, 1983-1984 (Box 243B, Folder 25)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: CWA City of Hope Program: Pledges, Contributions, 1980 (Box 243B, Folder 26)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: City of Hope Program Bank Account, 1981 (Box 243B, Folder 27)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: City of Hope Program Pledges, 1981 (Box 243B, Folder 28)
      - Long Lines: Grievances: City of Hope: Bike-A-Thon, 1981 (Box 243B, Folder 29)
      - District # 1- New York Tel. Co., 1949-1971 (Box 244, Folder 1)
      - District # 1- New York Tel. Co., 1971 (Box 244, Folder 2)
      - District # 1- New York Tel. Co., 1971-1972 (Box 244, Folder 3)
      - District # 1- New York Tel. Co. Contract., 1971-1972 (Box 244, Folder 4)
      - District # 1- Rochester Tel. Co., 1947-1951 (Box 244, Folder 5)
      - District # 1- W.E. Buffalo Plant, Div. #63, 1947-1951 (Box 244, Folder 6)
      - District # 1- W.E. Materials: Valley Works, 1949-1959 (Box 244, Folder 7)
      - District #1- Correspondence-Bargaining (Traffic Operators/Claire Glensan), 1960 (Box 244, Folder 8)
      - District # 1- Western Union, Agency Conversion Program/FCC Docket # 18908, 1970 (Box 244, Folder 9)